megazebra.com 2019-09-10

# Privacy Policy - MegaZebra

## **Privacy Policy for our Games**

MegaZebra GmbH, Steinsdorfstraße 2, 80538 München, Germany (“MegaZebra” or “we”), is a developer and publisher of games and mobile game applications that are made available via app stores including the Apple App Store, Google Play Store and Amazon Appstore, and other platforms such as Facebook (our “Games”). MegaZebra is responsible for providing Games and related services (such as support services, our website, competitions, newsletters, advertising etc.) (collectively, the “Services”) and for data processing. If you would like to find out more about MegaZebra and our Services, please visit the Imprint section of the Games or our Website [www.megazebra.com](http://www.megazebra.com/) .

In this data privacy policy, we will share what “personal data” or “personally identifiable data” mean, how we collect and what we do with the data, and why we do so. We will also let you know how we protect your data, when data will be deleted and which rights you as a data subject have. Personal data in this context are all individual information about personal or objective circumstances of a specific or identifiable natural person, e.g. your name, address or e-mail address, but also IP addresses and device-related identifiers. When you use our Games or access our Services, personal data is processed.

We hope to unite people in fun and enjoyment through our Games, so we create games that you can play and share with other people. This means that our Services can be accessed and shared with friends or in social networks. We believe that data protection is as important as uniting people through our Games and, therefore, we aim to protect your privacy as best as we can. If you use third party services – for example while playing one of our Games on Facebook – please note that those service providers will also collect personal data, that is not part of our service.

 **Who can I contact?**

MegaZebra GmbH is responsible for their Services and for the protection of your data as a player. You can reach us at:

 **MegaZebra GmbH** **  
****Steinsdorfstraße 2** **  
****80538 München** **  
****Germany**

 **Phone: +49 (0)89 80 92 95 77** **  
****Fax: +49 (0)89 81 30 02 82**

If you have specific questions about your personal data, deletion of your personal data or similar things, you can contact us via e-mail at [info@megazebra.com](mailto:info@megazebra.com)

 **What are my rights?**

You can contact us at any time if you have any questions about your rights regarding data protection or if you wish to exercise any of the following rights:

 **Right to withdraw your consent** in accordance with Art. 7 para. 3 GDPR (e.g. you can contact us if you wish to cancel a previously given consent to a newsletter)

 **Right to access your data** in accordance with Art. 15 GDPR (e.g. you can contact us if you would like to know what data we have stored about you)

 **Right to correct your data** in accordance with Art. 16 GDPR (e.g. you can contact us if your e-mail address has changed and we should replace your old e-mail address)

 **Right to have your data deleted** in accordance with Art. 17 GDPR (e.g. you can contact us if you want us to delete certain data that we have stored about you)

 **Right to limit data collection** in accordance with Art. 18 GDPR (e.g. you can contact us if you do not want us to use your e-mail address for newsletters, but only to send absolutely necessary e-mails)

 **Right to take your data with you** in accordance with Art. 20 GDPR (e.g. you can contact us to receive your data, if you want to upload it to another service)

 **Right to object how your data is handled** in accordance with Art. 21 GDPR (e.g. you can contact us if you do not agree with any user analytics procedures as described within this privacy policy)

 **Right to send complaints** to the supervisory authority in accordance with Art. 77 para. 1 f GDPR (e.g. you can contact the data protection supervisory authority directly)

 **Deletion of data and storage periods**

Unless otherwise stated, we will delete or anonymise your data as soon as it is no longer needed (e.g. your e-mail address after you have unsubscribed from our newsletter). Your data will also be deleted or anonymised automatically, if and when the mandatory storage period expires (e.g. those required by law for payment transactions). Such data may be needed for longer periods of time for legal reasons. You can request information about all personal data we have stored about you.

 **Data collected in our Games**

When you use our Services, we collect and store certain data about you to provide our Games and Services, to improve your overall user experience and to provide you with customised offers (e.g. certain in-game offers that you might like based on your playing behaviour):

 _Temporary unique device identifiers (e.g. IDFA and Android ID) and random device identification numbers (client IDs) and user identification numbers (user IDs)_

 _Progress in the game and playing behaviour (e.g. how fast you reached a certain level or how you decorated your house)_

 _In-app purchases (e.g. how many Diamonds you purchased for which price)_

 _Game version (e.g. v1.23.111)_

 _Language Settings (e.g. system language English)_

 _IP address (e.g. 96.92.316.example or 2a02:7122:8337:1112:bdb2:651f:example)_

 _Approximate location based on IP range (e.g. “Berlin & surrounding area”)_

 _Internet provider (e.g. “Unity Media“ or “Deutsche Telekom“)_

 _Internet connection speed (e.g. 120 Mbit)_

 _Date and time of your game session (e.g. 11:45 on 25.05.2018)_

 _Browser and version (e.g. Chrome v65 or Safari 11.1)_

 _Operating system (e.g. MacOS, Android)_

 _Hardware (e.g. Intel processor)_

You may be aware that your IP address and other unique identifiers can theoretically be traced back to you or to the device you are playing on. As a safeguard to protect your privacy, we delete or anonymise identifiers in our database and most of the technical data after your game session. Any other data will only be used for statistical purposes to optimise the game, to serve interest-based ads (more information can be found below under “(Personalised) Advertising”) and to offer a more personalised gaming experience to you as our players (e.g. automatically setting the difficulty depending on your playing behaviour). The purpose of temporarily storing this data is to establish a connection with our game servers which is necessary for providing our Games and Services as well as to provide a more personalised gaming experience to you. The legal basis are the contract with you in accordance with Art. 6 para. 1 lit. b GDPR and also the legitimate interest in accordance with the European data protection requirements under Art. 6 para. 1 lit. f GDPR. In addition, we apply the aforementioned safeguards to protect your data.

 **Mobile app and app permissions**

When downloading our Games as mobile apps or purchasing in-app items inside the Games through an app platform (e.g. Apple App Store or Google Play Store), you submit certain information to that platform, in particular your account data, e.g. your name, device identifiers, e-mail address and payment information. We have no influence on this data collection and are not responsible for it.

Some features of our Games require the app to access certain functions and services on your device. Depending on which mobile operating system you are using, this may require you to accept certain app permissions. We will now explain to you what those permissions are as follows:

 **iOS**

Push notifications: If you select OK in the “Allow push notifications” pop up, you allow the app to notify you of certain events inside the game, even if the app is not currently open. You will then receive alerts as sounds, messages and/or symbol indicators (an image or a number on the app icon).

Game Center: We also provide a connection to the Game Center service from Apple, which is subject to Apple’s Privacy Policy, available at [https://www.apple.com/privacy](https://www.apple.com/privacy/). When you use the service, e.g. to receive notifications about achievements, the personal information you share is visible to other users and can be read, collected, or used by them. You need to consider which personal information you choose to submit.

 **Android**

External Storage (Change or delete the contents of your external storage, read the contents of your external storage): These functions allow the app to temporarily store content on your device. The app only uses its own memory storage for this purpose. Other data on the external storage will not be erased, modified or read.

Internet Connection (Get Internet data, view full network access, network and Wi-Fi connections): These functions allow the app to obtain data from the Internet and to determine whether a connection to the Internet exists via a Wi-Fi network or via a mobile data connection. This is to prevent that larger amounts of data may use too much of limited data volumes.

Deactivate hibernation: This function allows the app to deactivate the idle state of the phone (e.g. to display videos without switching off the screen).

As a safeguard to protect your privacy, all app permissions are optional, except for the technical permissions needed for the app to run. You can always decline (by clicking “no” or “do not accept” in your device settings). You can also revoke app permissions afterwards by changing the corresponding settings on your device. The purpose of asking for those app permissions is to keep you and the game updated on game updates, game related news and notifications. The legal basis is your consent in accordance with the European data protection requirements under Art. 6 para. 1 lit. a GDPR.

 **Connecting with Facebook**

You can play some of our Games directly on Facebook or connect the game with your Facebook account details. If you do either of those, you will be able to use your Facebook account to log in on multiple devices and synchronise your saved game status across different devices. We will not store your friends lists and contacts and there is no permanent link between the game and your Facebook account, you can always disconnect your Facebook profile from the game you are playing. The underlying service is provided by Facebook and further details can be found in Facebook’s Privacy Policy (<http://www.facebook.com/policy.php>). The connection with Facebook will not allow us to post anything to your Facebook page without your permission. We will receive some of the following Facebook account information, depending on what you choose to provide:

P _ublic profile information (e.g. Facebook name, your profile picture and other public information etc.)_

 _Friends list (friends you are connected with on Facebook)_

 _E-Mail address (the e-mail address you use to log in to Facebook)_

 _Facebook game specific ID related to your profile and the game you are playing (not your Facebook ID)_

We use this information to improve your gaming experience (e.g. you can see which of your friends are playing the same game as you are and the other way around) and also for market research and advertising, but only following anonymisation.

As a safeguard to protect your privacy and the privacy of your friends, Facebook lets you choose which of your Facebook information you want to share with us (except for the required profile information) and we ensure that personal information is deleted or anonymised, so that it cannot be traced back to you in our systems. Since some of the Facebook services are located in the USA and thus in a country outside the EU and the EEA (a third country), further safeguards are required to ensure that your data is protected in accordance with a European level of data protection. Facebook has been certified under the EU-US Privacy Shield for the ad-related services and has thus demonstrated a sufficient level of data protection (<https://www.facebook.com/about/privacyshield>). The purpose of collecting and storing this information is to connect you with your friends on Facebook, to provide you with a cross-platform gaming experience, to synchronise your saved game status and to offer personalised advertising. The legal basis is your consent – when choosing to connect your Facebook account – in accordance with the European data protection requirements under Art. 6 para. 1 lit. a GDPR.

 **(Personalised) Advertising**

We use advertising technologies in our Games and exchange ad identifiers with external advertising networks to allow personalised advertising within our Games. We and our trusted partners collect and process the Apple Advertising ID (IDFA) on iOS devices and the Google Advertising ID on Android devices to allow interest-based advertising and measure the success of aforementioned advertising. Advertising IDs are unique but at the same time non-personalised and non-permanent identification numbers provided by your operating system and device. We will now explain how to activate or deactivate the advertising technologies within the mobile apps as follows:

 **iOS**

Open the “Settings” application of iOS and select the “Privacy” menu item and then the “Advertising” sub-item. If you activate the “Limit ad tracking” option, we can only take limited measures such as identifying unique users or combating fraud. In the same menu you can always delete the IDFA (“Reset Ad-ID”), then a new ID is created which is not merged with the data collected earlier.

 **Android**

Open the “Settings” application and select the “Google” menu item. Depending on your device, this option may not be visible on the main menu but you may use the search function at the top of the Settings menu to find it. From there, select the “Ads” sub-item and activate the option “Opt out of Ads Personalisation” to prevent the creation of profiles and the display of interest-based advertising. You can delete the advertising ID in the same menu at any time (“Reset advertising ID”), then a new ID will be created which will not be merged with the previously collected data.

As a safeguard to protect your privacy, we only store personal information temporarily. Additionally, the user can deactivate interest-based advertising in the device settings as described above. We also ensure that our external service providers are committed to a high level of data protection by concluding data protection agreements. The purpose is to improve our Games and provide the player with more relevant ads. The information collected helps us to improve our websites and Games and – at the same time – keep our Games free for a wide player base. The legal basis is the legitimate interest in accordance with the European data protection requirements under Art. 6 para. 1 lit. f GDPR, which we evaluated together with our data protection officer. In addition, a data processing agreements were concluded with external ad technology providers networks in accordance with the requirements of Art. 28 GDPR.

 **Last updated: May 2018**

### [ **DEUTSCHE VERSION**](http://www.megazebra.com/datenschutzerklarung/)

##  **Privacy Policy for the Applicant System  
**

We – MegaZebra  GmbH, Steinsdorfstr. 2 in 80538 Munich (hereinafter referred to as “MegaZebra” or “we”) collect and use your personal data that you provide to MegaZebra by way of the applicant system.

We wish to provide this data protection statement, which applies exclusively to data collected within the scope of the online application process, in order to inform you of the manner in which we handle your personal data collected in connection with the application process.

 **Personal data in connection with the application process**

Personal data refers to information about the personal or material circumstances of an identified or identifiable natural person. This includes information such as your name, your address, your telephone number and your date of birth, as well as data about your professional background etc., which can be assigned to an identified person with reasonable effort. Information that does not directly relate to your true identity, however, does not constitute personal data.

Under certain circumstances, special types of personal data may also be encompassed, such as information related to health, heritage, and religion, insofar as you disclose such data to us.

 **Collection and processing of personal data**

Our data protection rules comply with the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), the German Federal Data Protection Act (BDSG-neu) and the German Telemedia Act (TMG).

MegaZebra acts as the data controller. The cloud-based service provider BambooHR acts as data processor. The privacy policy of BambooHR can be found on their website.

If you are applying for a vacant position or are submitting a speculative application via the application system on our website, you voluntarily transmit personal data and information (first name, last name, email address, telephone number, as well as any attachments such as a resume, cover letter, etc.).

In the event that you submit a speculative application by email directly to [jobs@megazebra.com](mailto:jobs@megazebra.com), your data will typically be transmitted via an encrypted connection (transport encryption); however, end-to-end encryption cannot be guaranteed.

 **Storage of personal data**

Personal data is stored exclusively for the purpose of filling the vacant position for which you have applied.

In accordance with Section 17 GDPR,< we are required to delete your data if we no longer process it for our own purposes and knowledge thereof is no longer necessary for the fulfillment of the purpose. Following completion of the application process, we shall store your data for no longer than a statutorily permitted period of 6 months.

In the event you provide your consent, we will store your data in our talent pool following completion of the application process for a limited period of 2 years in order to identify any other interesting positions for you. You can provide your consent to inclusion in our talent pool by email

You may revoke your consent at any time and object to the storage of your data.

 **Deletion of personal data**

You may contact us at any time via [jobs@megazebra.com](mailto:jobs@megazebra.com) in order to request the deletion of your data.

After 6 months, your data will automatically be anonymized, unless you have provided your consent to inclusion in the talent pool. The data will then only be available to us as metadata for statistical analyses, without any direct connection to your identity (such as the proportion of men or women among applicants, number of applications per interval, etc.).

 **Disclosure of personal data**

Without your consent, we shall only disclose personal data in the following cases:

Should it be necessary for purposes of legal prosecution, personal data may be disclosed to the prosecuting authorities as well as any injured third parties. In this case, however, we must be given specific indications for unlawful or abusive conduct. Moreover, data may be disclosed if this disclosure serves to enforce terms of use or other agreements.

We are also legally obliged to provide information in the event of requests by certain public entities, such as prosecuting authorities, tax authorities, as well as authorities pursuing offenses that entail fines.

 **Security of your personal data**

Both we as a company and any employees involved in the application process are instructed to carry out appropriate organizational and technical measures in order to protect personal data against misuse, unauthorized disclosure and loss. These measures shall at least meet the requirements of Section 25 GDPR.

 **Right to information**

You have the right to request information about your stored data from us (Section 15 GDPR). In addition, pursuant to Section 16, 17 and 18 GDPR, you have the right to request us to correct, delete and block your personal data. Should you wish to exercise this right, please contact MegaZebra GmbH or send an email to [jobs@megazebra.com](mailto:jobs@megazebra.com).

 **Questions and comments**

If you have any questions about our information regarding data protection and the processing of your personal data, you may contact us directly. Please write to the following address:

 **MegaZebra GmbH** **  
****Steinsdorfstraße 2** **  
****80538 München** **  
****Germany**

or send an email to: [jobs@megazebra.com](mailto:jobs@megazebra.com)

 **Validity and amendments to the data protection rules for the applicant system**

The data protection statement is dated May 22, 2018. The ongoing development of our application process or the implementation of new features or technologies may necessitate amendments to these data protection rules. We reserve the right to carry out such changes at any time.

 **Last updated: May 2018**

##  **Privacy Policy for our Website**

We – MegaZebra GmbH, Steinsdorfstraße 2 in 80538 Munich (hereinafter referred to as “MegaZebra” or “we”) operate the website http://www.megazebra.com and are responsible for the collection, processing, and use of your personal data as defined by the German Federal Data Protection Act (BDSG) and the German Telemedia Act (TMG). Insofar as you have been directed to this data protection statement from one of our other websites, the following information applies accordingly.

We wish to provide the following data protection statement as information on how we handle your personal data. We believe the observance and maintenance of your privacy takes high priority, not only in the provision of our games, but also in connection with our websites and all other processes.

However, we would like to point out that online data transmission can entail security vulnerabilities. Seamless protection of data against access by third parties is not possible. We have taken the best possible technical and organizational measures to protect the security of your data against loss, destruction, willful manipulation and unauthorized access by third parties to the greatest extent possible.

In the event that you are directed by a link contained on a website operated by MegaZebra to another website that is not operated by MegaZebra, or you utilize the services of third parties (such as during a payment process), please note that the following data protection statement does not apply to these third-party websites.

 **Collection and use of your personal data**

Personal data in this sense refers to all individual pieces of information regarding the personal or material circumstances of an identified or identifiable natural person, such as name, address, or email address as well as IP address. If you visit our websites or use the contact form, the collection, processing, and use of personal data will take place.

We do not collect any personal data during simple visits to our websites, with the exception of data transmitted by your browser in order to enable the visit to the websites.

These include:

 _IP address_  
_Date and time of the request_  
_Content of the request (specific page)_  
_Access status / HTTP status code_  
_Any data quantities transmitted_  
_Website from which the request originates_  
_Browser_  
_Operating system_

We delete or anonymize the IP addresses of website visitors after the end of use. Anonymization means that the IP addresses are modified such that the individual details regarding personal or material circumstances can no longer be associated with an identified or identifiable natural person, or may only be associated to such a person with an unreasonable expenditure of time, costs and effort.

 **Contact options**

You can contact us using our contact form and submit questions and comments regarding our business areas. In order to use the contact form, you are required to enter additional personal information, such as your name and your email address, which we shall use and store in order to contact you. We shall only use the data for the underlying purpose and in accordance with data protection principles.

 **Cookies**

Our website sometimes uses cookies. Cookies serve to make our website more user-friendly, effective and secure. Cookies are small files that are stored on your device and contain certain settings and data for interaction with our system via your browser.

A distinction is generally made between two different types of cookies: Session cookies are deleted as soon as you close your browser (= end of session) and temporary/permanent cookies are stored on your data storage medium for either an extended period of time or without limitation. This storage helps us to design our website effectively and facilitates your use, for instance, by storing certain details about you so that you do not need to repeatedly enter them.

You can delete the cookies at any time via the security settings for your browser and configure your browser settings as you see fit (such as the acceptance of third-party cookies or rejection of all cookies). Generally, you will be shown how you can reject new cookies and delete existing cookies using the help function in the menu bar of your web browser. However, we wish to point out that you may then no longer be able to use all the features of our website.

 **Social plugins**

We use plugins for various social networks on our website.

a. Facebook

Facebook is operated by Facebook Inc., 1601 S. California Ave, Palo Alto, CA 94304, USA and can be accessed at http://www.facebook.com. These individual social plugins are marked by one of the Facebook logos or with the additional text “Facebook Social Plugin”. A list containing the appearance and functions of the individual plugins can be viewed here: http://developers.facebook.com/docs/plugins.

When you access a page of our website that contains such a social plugin, the browser you use will establish a direct connection with the servers of Facebook. The content of the social plugin will be transmitted directly from Facebook to your browser and integrated into the website by the browser. We therefore have no influence over the scope of data that Facebook collects using social plugins; we thus inform you in accordance with our level of knowledge.

Due to the integration of the social plugins, Facebook is informed that you have visited the corresponding page on our website, even if you are not registered as a user of Facebook or are not currently logged in on Facebook. This information is transmitted by your browser together with your IP address to a server of Facebook in the USA, where it is then stored. According to information provided by Facebook, only an anonymized IP address is stored for non-registered users in Germany. If you are logged in on Facebook, Facebook will be able to directly associate the visit to our website with your Facebook account. Facebook receives the information about your visit to our website regardless of whether you interact with the social plugins or not. If you interact with the social plugins, for example by pressing the “Like” button or submitting a comment, the relevant information is sent by your browser directly to Facebook, where it is then stored. The information is also published on Facebook and displayed to your Facebook friends. The purpose and scope of data collection and the further processing and use of data by Facebook as well as your corresponding rights and configuration options for protecting your privacy are stated in the data protection guidelines of Facebook. If you are a registered user of Facebook and do not wish for Facebook to collect data about you via our website and associate your visit with your account data stored at Facebook, you must first log out of Facebook before visiting our website. In addition, it is possible to block the social plugins using add-ons for your browser.

 **Data security**

We maintain up-to-date technical measures to ensure data security, especially for the protection of your personal data against dangers associated with data transmissions and access by third parties. These measures are accordingly updated to the state of the art.

 **Information, correction, and deletion**

You have a right, for example, to receive information free of charge regarding your stored data as well as a right to the correction, blocking, or deletion of data. If you would like to receive information regarding your stored data or further information regarding this data protection statement, please send your request by email or post to the following contact addresses:

 **MegaZebra GmbH** **  
****Steinsdorfstraße 2** **  
****80538 München** **  
****Germany**

 **Phone: +49 (0)89 80 92 95 77** **  
****Fax: +49 (0)89 81 30 02 82**

If you have specific questions about your personal data, deletion of your personal data or similar things, you can contact us via e-mail at [info@megazebra.com](mailto:info@megazebra.com)

 **Last updated: May 2018**
